

PROFILE

As a keen, 29 year old Junior Web Developer, I am enthusiastic and motivated young person, willing to learn new skills. I am currently at the Wild Code School and looking for a company based in Lyon or Paris where I could undertake an apprenticeship from 09/14/201 untill 09/13/2022.

SKILLS

Web and Mobile Development:

Frontend: JavaScript / React.js

React Native / Redux HTML / CSS / SASS

Backend: Node.js / Express.js

Database: MongoDb Workflow: Git / Github

Languages:

French: native

English: full professional proficiency

Soft skills:

Good Interpersonal Skills Team Work Curious Desire to learn

CANTIN BARTEL

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Tel. +32.470.13.42.29

www.linkedin.com/in/cantin-bartel

https://github.com/kontaba

https://cantinbartel.herokuapp.com

EDUCATION

Advanced Web and Mobile Development Formation - Apprenticeship from 14/09/2021 to 13/09/2022

Wild Code School - France

Web and Mobile Development Coding Bootcamp (2021)

La Capsule - Lyon France

Bachelor's degree in Aeronautical Engineering (2010-2014)

HEPH Condorcet - Charleroi Belgium

WORK EXPERIENCE

Avionics Aircraft Technician on Military Aircrafts (2018-2021)

SABCA - Charleroi Belgium

Working Holiday Visa Australia and New Zealand (2015 - 2018)